<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Techplex Labs</title><link>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Techplex Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 13:17:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techplexlabs.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Remarkable Line Simplification</title><link>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/remarkable-line-simplification/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 13:17:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/remarkable-line-simplification/</guid><description>I recently purchased a reMarkable 2 e-ink tablet with th goal of modernizing my note-taking process. My end goal is to make my handwritten notes searchable.
It seems the reMarkable is doing some sort of line simplification before sending the raw x, y coordinates to the MyScript Handwriting Recognition Service (HWR) service.
The following images show initial plotting of the line segements from the binary lines files vs the data sent by the tablet to the HWR service:</description></item><item><title>What Are the Red Green Bars on effects in xLights</title><link>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/what-are-the-red-green-bars-xlights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 21:47:38 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/what-are-the-red-green-bars-xlights/</guid><description>While working on importing the 2020 xLights around the world sequence &amp;ldquo;Into the Unknown&amp;rdquo; we noticed the red and green bars on some effects in the sequence. They look like this: After some prodding we dicovered the red line means transition out, whereas the green line indicates a transition in.
To create or edit a transition the controls on the Layer Blending menu.
Here is a sample effect with a fade transition in: Here is a sample effect with a fade transition out:</description></item><item><title>Cannot Render Onto Model... in xLights</title><link>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/cannot-render-onto-model/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techplexlabs.com/posts/cannot-render-onto-model/</guid><description>After importing the 2020 xLights around the world sequence &amp;ldquo;Into the Unknown&amp;rdquo; we noticed some of the effects we were attempting to map to our spiral pixel trees did not look as expected.
Running Tools &amp;gt; Check Sequence gave a cryptic error message in the &amp;ldquo;Effect problems&amp;rdquo; section.
WARN: Effect Video ends at 3:06.200 after the sequence end 3:06.000. Model: 'All Pixels' Start: 3:03.450 ERR: Video effect video file '/lightshow/sequences/imports/xLights ATW Into The Unknown/Video/Soft Illumination Blue with Wind.</description></item></channel></rss>